cfagbata.com 2013-11-28

# Privacy Policy - Author | Speaker | Coach | Digital Media Consultant | Business Expert

### Welcome to the Privacy Policy page of www.cfagbata.com, also Conditioned for Accomplishments (the “Site”).

We understand that privacy online is important to users of our Site and this policy governs our privacy policies with respect to those users of the Site (“Visitors”) who visit without transacting business and Visitors who register to transact business on the Site and make use of the various [services](http://www.cfagbata.com/services/ "services") offered by cfagbata.com (collectively, “[Services](http://www.cfagbata.com/services/ "Services")”) (“Authorized Customers”).

 **cfagbata.com respects your privacy**

Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released,

Privacy Policy

 sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of cfagbata.com

We have a strict no spam policy and do not send you any emails, unless you subscribe to receive email updates.

 **Credit card details**

cfagbata.com will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you **Do Not** enter it on any of the forms here. If there is a payment to be made you will be redirected to our merchant who processes the payment.

 **External Sites**

cfagbata.com is not responsible for the content of external Internet sites. You are advised to read the [privacy policy](http://www.cfagbata.com/privacy-policy/ "privacy policy") of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

 **Cookies**

A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows cfagbata.com to recognize you each time you visit this site (customization etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and cfagbata.com does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as news feeds.

 **Google and DoubleClick DART Cookies**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.

  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet.

  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network [privacy policy](http://www.cfagbata.com/privacy-policy/ "privacy policy").

 **Visitor Tracking**

cfagbata.com makes use of analytical software such as Google Analytics for statistical purposes. For the purpose of stats your IP (Internet Protocol) Address, browser, screen resolution, operating system are captured. We at cfagbata.com use this information only for statistical purpose and do not share it with any third party.

 **User Comments**

cfagbata.com allows users to comment on the site. However we hold all rights to accept or reject any comments based on our discretion. While commenting on cfagbata.com please refrain from using content that is not suitable or irrelevant to the various topics.

 **Remember the Risks whenever you Use the Internet**

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to cfagbata.com and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through cfagbata.com have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.

Please reach **** those webmasters and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

##  **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

cfagbata.com reserves the right to change, modify or update this policy at any time without notice. Any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information will be posted on this site.
